let SKIQUESTIONS = [
  { question: "What does wipe out mean?", 
     correct: "Falling over, usually in dramatic fashion", 
     answers: ["It's a popular apres dance move", 
     "Falling over, usually in dramatic fashion", 
     "Poor visibility on the slopes because it's snowing", 
     "Landing a trick" ]},
   
  { question: "What does bombing refer to?", 
    correct:  "Travelling at speed down the slope", 
    answers:  ["A night where you only drink Jagerbombs", 
    "It's slang for the Snowbombing festival in Mayrhofen", 
    "Breaking through the top crust of snow and sinking into deep powder", 
    "Travelling at speed down the slope"]},
   
  { question: "What does stomp mean?", 
    correct: "When you land a trick well", 
    answers: ["When you jump up and down to rid your skis or board of snow", 
    "An apres party where everyone dances on tables in their ski boots", 
    "A shot comprised of Baileys, whiskey and Cointreau", 
    "When you land a trick well" ]},
   
  { question: "What is a kicker?", 
    correct: "A home-made wedge in the snow built for performing small tricks", 
    answers: ["A home-made wedge in the snow built for performing small tricks", 
    "A type of snowboard, designed for doing tricks", 
    "A piste with a sharp bend in it", 
    "A skier who spends most of their time in the park"]},
   
  { question: "What is chatter?", 
    correct: "When your skis or snowboard shakes because of rough terrain", 
    answers: ["Talking while on a chairlift", 
    "Eating a plate of chips up the mountain", 
    "When your skis or snowboard shakes because of rough terrain", 
    "Comparing the number of runs you've done with someone else at the end of the day" ]},
   
  { question: "A liftie is...", 
    correct: "A chairlift operator", 
    answers: ["A chairlift operator", 
    "A ski trick where you lift one knee up and grab your ski", 
    "A type of lift on a nursery slope consisting of a moving rope that pulls you uphill", 
    "When you catch a lift down the mountain on a snowmobile" ]},
   
  { question: "What is jibbing?", 
    correct: "Riding something other than snow, such as rails, trees etc.", 
    answers: ["Landing flat on your back after a jump", 
    "To ride with the nose of your snowboard elevated; the equivalent of a wheelie on snow", 
    "Riding something other than snow, such as rails, trees etc.", 
    "Skiing or riding very well" ]},
   
  { question: "What's a dump?", 
    correct: "A gap of flesh between your goggles and helmet", 
    answers: ["A space between your head and your helmet, causing it to rattle around when you ski", 
    "A very wide gap between your skis", 
    "A gap of flesh on your wrists between gloves and base layer sleeves", 
    "A gap of flesh between your goggles and helmet" ]},
   
  { question: "As a beginner, you don't want a gaper gap. This is...", 
    correct: "A gap of flesh between your goggles and helmet", 
    answers: ["A space between your head and your helmet, causing it to rattle around when you ski", 
    "A very wide gap between your skis", 
    "A gap of flesh on your wrists between gloves and base layer sleeves", 
    "A gap of flesh between your goggles and helmet" ]},
   
  { question: "Do you want to end up being a shredder or a ripper?", 
    correct: "Either. They are both compliments for accomplished skiers and snowboarders", 
    answers: ["Either. They are both compliments for accomplished skiers and snowboarders", 
    "Shredder. This is a term for a good skier or rider, while ripper refers to someone who falls over frequently", 
    "Ripper. This is a term for a good skier or rider, while shredder refers to someone who falls over frequently", 
    "Neither. They are both insults for unaccomplished skiers and snowboarders" ]},
];
  